linkstreet.in 2019-06-23

# Privacy Policy - RapL

Linkstreet is committed to protecting its visitors’ and Users’ privacy. The following Privacy and Cookie Policy outlines the information Linkstreet (hereafter “Linkstreet”, “we”, or “us”) may process and how we may use that information to better serve visitors and Users while using our website www.linkstreet.in (the ‘Website’) our mobile customer application (the ‘App’) and our on-demand services (collectively the “Service”). Please review the following carefully so that you understand our privacy practices. This Privacy and Cookie Policy was last changed on 5th June,2017.

###### DEFINITIONS

“User” means a person who has signed up and is registered with Linkstreet for the use or potential use of the Service. “Partner” means Stores, businesses or establishments using Linkstreet services to interact with customers or employees.

###### GENERAL

“Linkstreet” is a mobile application that connects businesses with their employees and customers. Linkstreet is only a service tool (not a service provider) and is designed, developed & conceptualized by Linkstreet. All Linkstreet services are rendered by Linkstreet under the name ‘Linkstreet’. Linkstreet is product development company, located at 2338, BDA Main Road, Jeevanbhimanagar, HAL Post, Bangalore 560017. All the rights, benefits, liabilities & obligations under the following terms & conditions shall accrue to the benefit of Linkstreet. (together with its subsidiaries and other affiliates hereinafter referred to as “us”, “We” or “Linkstreet” ).

###### FOR WHAT PURPOSES DO WE PROCESS YOUR PERSONAL DATA

  *  **Customer Service :**  When you register as a User, we will collect your name, email address and mobile phone number. We will use your contact details to send you a welcoming notification to verify your username and password, to communicate with you in response to your inquiries, and to send you service related announcements, for instance, if our Service is temporarily suspended for maintenance. We will use your registration information to create and manage your Linkstreet account.
  *  **Enhancing your Linkstreet Experience Geo Location Information :  **When you use the Linkstreet service, and only if you have consented thereto, we may utilize your geo location information, on a real time basis. We use this information to allow you to view offers around you. We may also use this real time geo location information to address user support, technical, or business issues that may arise in the course of your use of the service. Your mobile device informs you when network based geo location is utilized under the device location settings and by displaying the GPS arrow icon for GPS based locations.

###### PUSH NOTIFICATIONS

Linkstreet and its Partners will have the ability to contact you via push notifications on the RapL.

###### Linkstreet PROMOTIONS

Linkstreet may use your contact details to send you general updates regarding Linkstreet news, special offers and promotions.

###### GENERATING MANAGEMENT INFORMATION AND STATISTICAL DATA

Linkstreet uses your personal data in an anonymized and aggregated form to closely monitor which features of the Service are used most, to analyze usage patterns and to determine where we should offer or focus our Service. Linkstreet does not share any personal data with third parties other than analytics info with the respective partner.

###### OUR DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION

We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate or provide the Service on our behalf, to process payment if any, provide customer support, to perform Website related services (e.g., without limitation, maintenance services, database management, web analytics and improvement of the Website’s features) or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used. These third parties have limited access to your personal information only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are contractually bound not to disclose or use it for any other purpose. Linkstreet will disclose your personal data to the extent that this is legally required, or necessary for the establishment, exercise or defense of legal claims and legal process or in the event of an emergency pertaining to your health and/or safety.

###### YOUR RIGHTS

As a user, you have the right to information regarding your personal account, including information that you’ve provided to us and information regarding services availed on RapL. You may at any time request correction or erasure of your personal data, and object to any processing of your personal data by emailing us at support@getrapl.com. We will respond to your access and/or correction request within 48 business hours. You may also amend your personal details using your Linkstreet account.

###### RETENTION

Unless specified otherwise in this Privacy and Cookie Policy, we will retain your information until you cancel your Linkstreet account, or until your Linkstreet account has been inactive for a year. If you wish to cancel your Linkstreet account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services, please contact us at support@getrapl.com. After deletion of your account we will anonymize your data, unless these data are necessary to comply with a legal obligation or resolve disputes.

###### SECURITY

Linkstreet has taken appropriate technical and organizational security measures against loss or unlawful processing of your personal data. To this purpose, your personal data are securely stored within our database, and we use standard, industry wide, commercially reasonable security practices such as encryption, firewalls and SSL (Secure Socket Layers) as well as physical safeguards of the locations where data are stored. However, as effective as encryption technology is, no security system is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee the security of our database, nor can we guarantee that information you supply won’t be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the Internet. Any transmission of information by you to Linkstreet is at your own risk. We recommend that you do not disclose your password to anyone.

###### CHANGES IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY

We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email and by means of a notice on the Website prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices. If you have questions about this Privacy and Cookie Policy, please contact us at support@getrapl.com.
